bee.com.eg 2012-11-10

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ”. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” collects, and the ways in which TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” uses that personal information.

## Personal Information Collection

TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * Information about your usage of this website including the pages you visit, the time you spent on each page and the order of browsing of these pages. 
  * Information that you provide for the purpose of registering with the website. 
  * Any other information that you share with TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ”.

## Using Personal Information

TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” may use your personal information to:

  * Administer this website.
  * Enable you to access and to use of the website services.
  * If you are one of our agents, publish information about your outlet(s) on the website.
  * Offer you certain services.
  * Send you marketing communications, such as updates and newsletters.
  * Generate the statistics and reports about your usage pattern.

Where TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” discloses your personal information to its partners for these purposes, the partner in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

## Securing your Data

  * TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
  * TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

## Cross Border Data Transfers

Information that TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” or any of its affiliates or parent companies operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

You agree to such cross border transfers of personal information.

## Updating this Statement

TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website without notifying the updates.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

## Other Websites

This website contains links to other websites.

TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

## Contact TBE Egypt “Bee”

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ”'s treatment of your personal information, please report this by email to [info@bee.com.eg](mailto:info@bee.com.eg) or by post to TBE Egypt “ **Bee** ” at their address: 27, Street 10, Block 63, Mahatta Square, Maadi, Cairo, Egypt.

Also, you can call us anytime 24/7 on our dedicated call center at 16BEE (16233), and you can inquire about any of Bee services and also about the nearest “Bee” outlet to you.
